Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - T-Z
        - Village People - Cruisin', 1978; SR-29243; Village People (Box 77)
          Catalog # NBLP 7118; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7118-AS
        - Vincent, Francky - Manze Lola, 1988; SR-29244; Vincent, Francky (Box 77)
          Catalog # 82422-1; A-side Matrix # MPO AM 82 422-1 A
          Bleu Caraibes
        - Visage - The damned don't cry, 1982; SR-29245; Visage (Box 77)
          Catalog # PRO 178; A-side Matrix # A-1 PRO-178-AS-HRM
        - Voice Farm - The world we live in, 1982; SR-29246; Voice Farm (Box 77)
          Catalog # Optional Records-004; A-side Matrix # VF 8067-A AUTOMATT/PS L-8321
          Optional Records
        - Von Wernherr, Otto - The saga of Bernhard Goetz, 1985; SR-29247; Von Wernherr, Otto (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29248. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MRS101; A-side Matrix # MRS 101 A
          Mindfield Records
        - Von Wernherr, Otto - The saga of Bernhard Goetz, 1985; SR-29248; Von Wernherr, Otto (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29247. 2 copies.
        - Voyage - Souvenirs, 1978; SR-29249; Voyage (Box 77)
          Catalog # TKD-117; A-side Matrix # TKD 117 A
        - Voyeur - Trick baby, 1985; SR-29250; Voyeur (Box 77)
          Catalog # MCA-23569; A-side Matrix # MCA-4621-SS1
        - Walden, Narada Michael - The dance of life, 1979; SR-29251; Walden, Narada Michael (Box 77)
          Catalog # SD 19259; A-side Matrix # ST-A-795391-C 0-1 SM 2-1 (PR)
        - Walden, Narada Michael - Victory, 1980; SR-29252; Walden, Narada Michael (Box 77)
          Catalog # SD 19279; A-side Matrix # ST-A-804535-B 0-1SM2-2
        - Walden, Narada Michael - I cry, I smile, 1977; SR-29253; Walden, Narada Michael (Box 77)
          Catalog # SD 19141; A-side Matrix # ST-A-773929-A (PR)P
        - Walker, Bobbi - Diamond in the rough, 1980; SR-29254; Walker, Bobbi (Box 77)
          Catalog # NBLP 7227; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7227-AS-X RC
        - Walker, Bobbi - Bobbi Walker, 1982; SR-29255; Walker, Bobbi (Box 77)
          Catalog # AAB-11016; A-side Matrix # M-11016-AS-P1
          Alfa
        - Junior Walker And The All-Stars - Hot shot, 1976; SR-29256; Junior Walker And The All-Stars (Box 77)
          Catalog # S6-745S1; A-side Matrix # S6-7451-2551-5-03D #13
        - Wallen - À force de vivre (disc one), 2001; SR-29257; Wallen (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29258. Double album.
          Catalog # ATM 2402-1; A-side Matrix # MPO A2402-1 A RV-TR
          Atmosphériques
        - Wallen - À force de vivre (disc two), 2001; SR-29258; Wallen (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29257. Double album.
          Catalog # ATM 2402-1; A-side Matrix # MPO A2402-1 C RV-TR
        - PaulAdamWalter - Brutal house, 1998; SR-29259; PaulAdamWalter; Walter, Leo; Paul, Kai; Adam, Michael Briston (Box 77)
          Catalog # 74321587641; A-side Matrix # B 812456-01 A1 KL
          Nextfire Recordings
        - War - The music band 2, 1979; SR-29260; War (Box 77)
          Catalog # MCA-3193; A-side Matrix # MCA-2037 CR-1 Wavy
        - War - All day music, 1971; SR-29261; War (Box 77)
          Catalog # UAS-5546; A-side Matrix # T UAS-5546-A-3
          United Artists Records
        - Ware, Leon - Rockin' you eternally, 1981; SR-29262; Ware, Leon (Box 77)
          Catalog # 6E-332; A-side Matrix # 6E332-A 1-1
        - Guy Warren Sounds - Themes for African drums, 1959; SR-29263; Guy Warren Sounds (Box 77)
          Catalog # LSP 1864; A-side Matrix # J2 PY5339-1S A2 I
        - Warwick, Dionne - Here I am, 1966; SR-29264; Warwick, Dionne (Box 77)
          Catalog # SPS 531; A-side Matrix # ae Brown SPS531A-3A PP audiospectrum
          Scepter Records
        - Warwick, Dionne - Hot! Live and otherwise (disc one), 1981; SR-29265; Warwick, Dionne (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29266. Double album.
          Catalog # A2L 8605; A-side Matrix # A2L-8605-SA-X
          Arista
        - Warwick, Dionne - Hot! Live and otherwise (disc two), 1981; SR-29266; Warwick, Dionne (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29265. Double album.
          Catalog # A2L 8605; A-side Matrix # A2L-8605-SC-X
        - Warwick, Dionne - Dionne, 1979; SR-29267; Warwick, Dionne (Box 77)
          Catalog # AB 4230; A-side Matrix # AB-4230-St AZ HuB
        - Warwick, Dionne - The collection (disc one), 1983; SR-29268; Warwick, Dionne (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29269. Double album.
          Catalog # DIONE I; A-side Matrix # DIONE-I-A tone MT DAMONT
        - Warwick, Dionne - The collection (disc two), 1983; SR-29269; Warwick, Dionne (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29268. Double album.
          Catalog # DIONE I; A-side Matrix # DIONE-I-C 2 MT DAMONT
        - Was (Not Was) - Was (Not Was), 1981; SR-29270; Was (Not Was) (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29271. Different discs.
          Catalog # ILPS 9666; A-side Matrix # ILPS-1-9666-S1 + SLM + 681 (SUB) B-15800-S1
        - Was (Not Was) - Out come the freaks, 1981; SR-29271; Was (Not Was) (Box 77)
          In same jacket as # SR-29270. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-961; A-side Matrix # B-15833-A2 VDNOS PRO-A1-961-A2
        - Washington, Deborah - Rock it, 1979; SR-29272; Washington, Deborah (Box 77)
          Catalog # PRO 7772; A-side Matrix # S PRO-7772- AS-LONG-2
          Ariola Records America
        - Washington, Grover Jr. - Just the two of us, 1980; SR-29273; Washington, Grover Jr. (Box 78)
          Catalog # AS-11483; A-side Matrix # AS 11483-A-SP-1A
        - Washington, Grover Jr. - Live at the Bijou (disc one), 1977; SR-29274; Washington, Grover Jr. (Box 78)
          In same jacket as # SR-29275. Double album.
          Catalog # KX-3637 M2; A-side Matrix # T\ RVG-98796-143 CTH J-6
          Kudu
        - Washington, Grover Jr. - Live at the Bijou (disc two), 1977; SR-29275; Washington, Grover Jr. (Box 78)
          In same jacket as # SR-29274. Double album.
          Catalog # KX-3637 M2; A-side Matrix # T1 98797-A 10 CTH A
        - Washington, Grover Jr. - Skylarkin', 1980; SR-29276; Washington, Grover Jr. (Box 78)
          Catalog # M7-933R1; A-side Matrix # M7-933-R1-A-SIDE 13A
        - Waters - Watercolors, 1980; SR-29277; Waters (Box 78)
          Catalog # AB 4253; A-side Matrix # AB4253-SA -1D HuB
        - Ed Watson And The Brass Circle - Constant carnival jammin, 1976; SR-29278; Ed Watson And The Brass Circle (Box 78)
          Catalog # GS 8888; A-side Matrix # GS888-A
          Straker's Records
        - Watson, Johnny Guitar - That's what time it is, 1981; SR-29279; Watson, Johnny Guitar (Box 78)
          Catalog # SP-4880; A-side Matrix # A+M SP 04880A-P4
        - Watsonian Institute - Extra disco perception, 1979; SR-29280; Watsonian Institute (Box 78)
          Catalog # DJM 27; A-side Matrix # DJM-27-A-2-1-2
          DJM Records
        - Watts, Brenda - Who needs a love like that, 1982; SR-29281; Watts, Brenda (Box 78)
          Catalog # EMDS 6531; A-side Matrix # HERbIE Jr EMDS-6531-A SMK
          Emergency Records
        - Watts, Ernie - Sanctuary, 1986; SR-29282; Watts, Ernie (Box 78)
          Catalog # 1-25513; A-side Matrix # SP 0-1 1-25513-A SH-3 B-24719-SH3 13634
          Qwest Records
        - Watty, Jay and Quiet Hit Men - 2 much noize; Bounce 2 dis; Mother; Got that booty, 1997; SR-29283; Watty, Jay; Quiet Hit Men (Box 78)
          In same jacket as # SR-29284. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SOB-02; A-side Matrix # SOB 02-A
          S.O.B. Entertainment
          Maryland
        - Watty, Jay and Quiet Hit Men - 2 much noize; Bounce 2 dis; Mother; Got that booty, 1997; SR-29284; Watty, Jay; Quiet Hit Men (Box 78)
          In same jacket as # SR-29283. 2 copies.
        - Wax - Get loose, 1981; SR-29285; Wax (Box 78)
          Catalog # JD-12325; A-side Matrix # PD12325-A
        - Wax - Get loose, 1981; SR-29286; Wax (Box 78)
          Catalog # PD-12325; A-side Matrix # STERLING PD12325-A
        - Wax - Do you believe in magic, 1981; SR-29287; Wax (Box 78)
          In same jacket as # SR-29288. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AFL1-3918; A-side Matrix # AFL1-3918-A
        - Wax - Do you believe in magic, 1981; SR-29288; Wax (Box 78)
          In same jacket as # SR-29287. 2 copies.
        - Way of the West - Drum, 1981; SR-29289; Way of the West (Box 78)
          Catalog # DRUM 12; A-side Matrix # DRUM 12 A//1 E C
        - WC and the Maad Circle - Ghetto serenade; Hood rat; Caught n a fad, 1991; SR-29290; WC and the Maad Circle (Box 78)
          Catalog # SPRO 6624; A-side Matrix # S-26539 SPRO 6624 A Z 1
          Priority Records
        - Weapons of Peace - Weapons of Peace, 1977; SR-29291; Weapons of Peace (Box 78)
          Catalog # PZ 34747; A-side Matrix # AL-34747-1D
          Playboy Records
        - Weather Girls - The Weather Girls, 1988; SR-29292; Weather Girls (Box 78)
          Catalog # C 40778; A-side Matrix # AL 40778-1A-DMM G2 MASTERDISK DMM C1
        - Weather Report - Heavy weather, 1977; SR-29293; Weather Report (Box 78)
          Catalog # PC 34418; A-side Matrix # PAL-34418-1D
        - Weatherman - Life!, 1982; SR-29294; Weatherman (Box 78)
          Catalog # PRE 21-12; A-side Matrix # PRE 2112 A//1 42 0 T
          PRE Records
        - Webster, Joel - Elixir, 1974; SR-29295; Webster, Joel (Box 78)
          Catalog # CR 9004; A-side Matrix # CR-9004A TML-M
          Crossover Records
        - Wee Gee - Hold on (to your dreams); Ain't nothin' missin' (but the music), 1979; SR-29296; Wee Gee (Box 78)
          Catalog # DMD 228; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-38226-1 SM1-1 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D.K.
          Cotillion
        - Wee Papa Girl Rappers - The beat, the rhyme, the noise, 1989; SR-29297; Wee Papa Girl Rappers (Box 78)
          Catalog # 1172-1-J; A-side Matrix # MISF1 SM1 H IMP#1: 1172-1-JA
        - Weeks, Michelle - Don't give up (part 2), 1997; SR-29298; Weeks, Michelle (Box 78)
          Catalog # MOSR122; A-side Matrix # MOSR 122 A-2-1-1
          Ministry of Sound
        - Weisberg, Tim - Travelin' light, 1981; SR-29299; Weisberg, Tim (Box 78)
          Catalog # MCA-5245; A-side Matrix # MCA-2699-ML-7 TML-M MR A 25264 S27
        - Well Red - Yes we can, 1987; SR-29300; Well Red (Box 78)
          Catalog # 70514; A-side Matrix # 70514 A 1 M6 356099 2
        - Wells, Jean - I just can't stop dancing, 1979; SR-29301; Wells, Jean (Box 78)
          Catalog # 60; A-side Matrix # TEC-60-A-1A
          TEC Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Welsman, Carol - Just imagination, 1987; SR-29302; Welsman, Carol (Box 78)
          Catalog # 240 726-1; A-side Matrix # 240726 1 A 1 TM M6 358212 2
        - Wendy & Lisa - Fruit at the bottom, 1989; SR-29303; Wendy & Lisa (Box 78)
          Catalog # C 44341; A-side Matrix # MASTERDISK AL-44341-2A DMM G1
        - Wesley, Fred - Say blow by blow backwards, 1979; SR-29304; Wesley, Fred; Horny Horns; Parker, Maceo (Box 78)
          Catalog # SD 19254; A-side Matrix # ST-A794343-A MP A XIN 7 - (PR) SP
        - West Coast Crew - In the mix, 1985; SR-29305; West Coast Crew (Box 78)
          Catalog # KMA-LP-001; A-side Matrix # L-10700-KMA-LP-1-A
          KMA Records
          Northridge, California
        - West Indian Tobacco Desperadoes - The best of despers, 1977; SR-29306; West Indian Tobacco Desperadoes (Box 78)
          Catalog # CR 6391; A-side Matrix # RHYNEL REC 6391 SIDE 1
        - WestBam - Terminator, 1996; SR-29307; WestBam (Box 78)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # WESTBAM-TERMINATOR-A-(four to the floor)
          Low Spirit Recordings
        - WestBam - We'll never stop living this way (Disc one), 1998; SR-29308; WestBam (Box 78)
          In same jacket as # SR-29309. Double album.
          Catalog # 40 14235 251836; A-side Matrix # WESTBAM-A1 Seite 1
        - WestBam - We'll never stop living this way (Disc two), 1998; SR-29309; WestBam (Box 78)
          In same jacket as # SR-29308. Double album.
          Catalog # 40 14235 251836; A-side Matrix # WESTBAM-A1 Seite 3
        - WestBam - Saxophone, 1989; SR-29310; WestBam (Box 78)
          Catalog # CYGT 2; A-side Matrix # 89 _I 1 CYGT 2-A\
          Cygnet Records
        - WestBam - Saxophone, 1989; SR-29311; WestBam (Box 78)
        - WestBam - ...And more, 1997; SR-29312; WestBam; Can (Box 78)
          Catalog # 74321 46427 1; A-side Matrix # WESTBAM-A1
          Loud & Slow
        - Wham - Wham, 1978; SR-29313; Wham (Box 78)
          Catalog # GRT-8025; A-side Matrix # GRT XSX-149169-1A GRT-8025-A-REI
          GRT
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - Whatnauts - Help is on the way, 1981; SR-29314; Whatnauts (Box 78)
          Catalog # H.I.R. 110; A-side Matrix # HIR-110-A MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE TEE
          Harlem International Records, Inc.
        - Whispers - Happy holidays to you, 1979; SR-29315; Whispers (Box 78)
          Catalog # BXL1-3489; A-side Matrix # A1 F BXL1-3489-A 1S MASTERED BY CAPITOL Wally
          Solar
        - Whispers - This kind of lovin', 1981; SR-29316; Whispers (Box 78)
          In same jacket as # SR-29317. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JD-12299; A-side Matrix # A 2 YD-12299-A 1S MASTERED BY CAPITOL Wally
        - Whispers - This kind of lovin', 1981; SR-29317; Whispers (Box 78)
          In same jacket as # SR-29316. 2 copies.
        - Whispers - The Whispers, 1979; SR-29318; Whispers (Box 78)
          Catalog # BXL1-3521; A-side Matrix # K-11557 BXL1-3521A-16 GoL
        - Whistle - Transformation, 1988; SR-29319; Whistle (Box 78)
          Catalog # SEL 21625; A-side Matrix # A-1 SEL-21625-A HERbIE JR
        - Whitaker, Eloise - Eloise Whitaker, 1981; SR-29320; Whitaker, Eloise (Box 78)
          Catalog # DLA-10006; A-side Matrix # DLC-10006-A PRC-1 -1-1 MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ L.A., CALIF.
          Destiny Records
        - White, Barry - The message is love, 1979; SR-29321; White, Barry (Box 78)
          Catalog # JZ 35763; A-side Matrix # PAL 3576316
          Unlimited Gold
        - White, Barry - Just another way to say I love you, 1975; SR-29322; White, Barry (Box 78)
          Catalog # T-466; A-side Matrix # M-466-AS XX
          20th Century Records
        - White, Barry - I love to sing the songs I sing, 1979; SR-29323; White, Barry (Box 78)
          Catalog # T-590; A-side Matrix # M590 ASA 16
          20th Century Fox Records
        - White, Barry - Just another way to say I love you, 1975; SR-29324; White, Barry (Box 78)
        - White, Barry - It ain't love, babe (until you give it), 1979; SR-29325; White, Barry (Box 78)
          Catalog # 4Z8-1403; A-side Matrix # 4S8-1403-3AC
        - White, James - Sax maniac, 1982; SR-29326; White, James; Blacks (Box 78)
          Catalog # APE 6002; A-side Matrix # P T APE-6002-A-CT2
        - White, Karyn - Karyn White, 1988; SR-29327; White, Karyn (Box 78)
          Catalog # 1-25637; A-side Matrix # 1-25637-A-SR2
        - White, Lenny - Big city, 1977; SR-29328; White, Lenny (Box 79)
          Catalog # NE 441; A-side Matrix # ST-NE-763781-BBB-1 AT
          Nemperor Records
        - White, Tony Joe - The real thang, 1980; SR-29366; White, Tony Joe (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29367. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NBLP 7233; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7233-A-Rei SP-3
        - White, Tony Joe - The real thang, 1980; SR-29367; White, Tony Joe (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29366. 2 copies.
        - Whiteface - Whiteface, 1979; SR-29368; Whiteface (Box 79)
          Catalog # SRM-1-3765; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-3765-A5-1-1
        - Whiteface - Live at the Agora, 1979; SR-29369; Whiteface (Box 79)
          Catalog # MK-103; A-side Matrix # T1 MK-103-A
        - Whiteside, Bobby - Bittersweet stories, 1974; SR-29370; Whiteside, Bobby (Box 79)
          Catalog # CRS 8603; A-side Matrix # CRS-8603-A-2
          Curtom
        - Whitfield, Norman - The songs of Norman Whitfield, 1976; SR-29371; Whitfield, Norman (Box 79)
          Catalog # PRO #7; A-side Matrix # PRO-7-JOB-121-S-A-07 VM 20515(1)
          Jobete Music Co., Inc.
        - Who - Tommy-original soundtrack recording (disc one), 1975; SR-29372; Who; Clapton, Eric; Turner, Tina (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29373. Double album.
          Catalog # PD-2-9502; A-side Matrix # TI PD2-9502-1
        - Who - Tommy-original soundtrack recording (disc two), 1975; SR-29373; Who; Clapton, Eric; Turner, Tina (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29372. Double album.
        - Whodini - Escape, 1984; SR-29374; Whodini (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29375. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JL 6-8251; A-side Matrix # JL-6-8251-SA
        - Whodini - Escape, 1984; SR-29375; Whodini (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29374. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JL 8-8267; A-side Matrix # JL8 8267 SA
        - Wild Boyz - It had to be done, 1989; SR-29376; Wild Boyz (Box 79)
          Catalog # V-3404; A-side Matrix # V-3404 A1
          Volt
        - Wild Cherry - Wild Cherry, 1976; SR-29377; Wild Cherry (Box 79)
          Catalog # PE 34195; A-side Matrix # AL-34195-1C
        - Wild Fantasy - Jungle drum, 1978; SR-29378; Wild Fantasy (Box 79)
          Catalog # MSI 003; A-side Matrix # MSI-003-A-2
          Midsong International
        - Wilde, Kim - Close, 1988; SR-29379; Wilde, Kim (Box 79)
          Catalog # 255 588-1; A-side Matrix # R/S Alsdorf 255588-1-AXX
        - Wildman Steve - The six thousand dollar nigger, 1977; SR-29380; Wildman Steve (Box 79)
          Catalog # LP-2030; A-side Matrix # WW-2030-A
          Weird World
        - Willesden Dodgers - More Jive rhythm trax, 1982; SR-29381; Willesden Dodgers (Box 79)
          Catalog # VA 66003; A-side Matrix # VA-66003-SA
        - Willesden Dodgers - Jive scratch trax (disc one), 1983; SR-29382; Willesden Dodgers (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29383. Double album.
          Catalog # JL 8 8105; A-side Matrix # JL-8-8105-SA
        - Willesden Dodgers - Jive scratch trax (disc two), 1983; SR-29383; Willesden Dodgers (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29382. Double album.
          Catalog # JL 8 8105; A-side Matrix # JL-8-8105-SC
        - Willesden Dodgers - More Jive rhythm trax, 1982; SR-29384; Willesden Dodgers (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29385. 2 copies.
        - Willesden Dodgers - More Jive rhythm trax, 1982; SR-29385; Willesden Dodgers (Box 79)
        - Williams, Alyson - Cooked (The remix album), 1989; SR-29386; Williams, Alyson (Box 79)
          Catalog # 466799 1; A-side Matrix # 01 455799 20 IA 1
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Williams, Andre - Rib tips & pig snoots, 2000; SR-29387; Williams, Andre (Box 79)
          Catalog # STS LP 6345; A-side Matrix # STS LP 6345 A
          Soul-Tay-Shus
        - Williams, Andre - Rib tips & pig snoots, 2000; SR-29388; Williams, Andre (Box 79)
        - Williams, Bobby - Funky super fly, 1974; SR-29389; Williams, Bobby (Box 79)
          Catalog # LP 330-1; A-side Matrix # LP 330 A
          R&R Records
          Miami, Florida
        - Williams, Bobby - Funky super fly, 1974; SR-29390; Williams, Bobby (Box 79)
        - Williams, Carol - No one can do it (like you) (Special re-mix: Shep Pettibone), 1981; SR-29391; Williams, Carol; Pettibone, Shep (Box 79)
          Catalog # SPV 52; A-side Matrix # SPV 52 A -1A
          Vanguard Disco
          Santa Monica, California
        - Williams, Carol - No one can do it (like you), 1981; SR-29392; Williams, Carol (Box 79)
          Catalog # SPV 47; A-side Matrix # SPV 47 A -2C
        - Williams, Deniece - This is Niecy, 1976; SR-29393; Williams, Deniece (Box 79)
          Catalog # PC 34242; A-side Matrix # PAL 34242-AC
        - Duke Williams and the Extremes - A monkey in a silk suit is still a monkey, 1973; SR-29394; Duke Williams and the Extremes (Box 79)
          Catalog # CP 0119; A-side Matrix # CP-0119 40570-A-1A
          Capricorn Records
          Macon, Georgia
        - Williams, Esther - Bustin' out, 1978; SR-29395; Williams, Esther (Box 79)
          Catalog # FS 112; A-side Matrix # 72114-A-RC
          Friends & Co.
        - Williams, Lenny - Taking chances, 1980; SR-29396; Williams, Lenny (Box 79)
          Catalog # MCA-5253; A-side Matrix # MCA 2712-AMI
        - Williams, Wanda "Star" - Soap opera lover, 1981; SR-29397; Williams, Wanda "Star" (Box 79)
          Catalog # 461; A-side Matrix # DASH-461-A
        - Williams, Wilson - Up the downstairs, 1978; SR-29398; Williams, Wilson (Box 79)
          Catalog # AA-1077; A-side Matrix # AA-1077-A
          ABC Records
        - Wilson, Charlie - Sprung on me, 1992; SR-29399; Wilson, Charlie (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29400. Different discs.
          Catalog # MCA8P 2223; A-side Matrix # MCA-11227 B6-1
        - Wilson, Charlie - Sprung on me, 1992; SR-29400; Wilson, Charlie (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29399. Different discs.
          Catalog # MCA12 54394; A-side Matrix # MCA11225 B6-2
        - Wilson, Charlie - Absolutely (Miss Cherokee remix; Mr President remix), 2001; SR-29401; Wilson, Charlie; Miss Cherokee; MC Cluedo (Box 79)
          Catalog # URSDJ8; A-side Matrix # URSDJ8-A 33 OPLAKE
          Urbanstar
        - Wilson, Jackie - Nobody but you, 1975; SR-29402; Wilson, Jackie (Box 79)
          Catalog # BL 754212; A-side Matrix # BMG 5073-1B
        - Wilson, Lesette - Now that I've got your attention, 1981; SR-29403; Wilson, Lesette (Box 79)
          Catalog # HF-9708; A-side Matrix # 9708 A PRECISION LACQUER S-8854 + SLM+ 940 HF
          Headfirst
        - Wilson, Shanice - Discovery, 1987; SR-29404; Wilson, Shanice (Box 79)
          Catalog # SP-5128; A-side Matrix # SP-05128-A ES1
        - Winans - Introducing The Winans, 1981; SR-29405; Winans (Box 79)
          Catalog # LS-5792; A-side Matrix # LS-5792 1-60089-A-SP 1-1 SM1
          Light Records
        - Winners - Winners, 1978; SR-29332; Winners (Box 79)
          Catalog # RS-LA868-H; A-side Matrix # STERLING RS-LA-868-1 MO
        - Winter, Edgar - The Edgar Winter Album, 1979; SR-28483; Winter, Edgar (Box 79)
          Catalog # JZ 35989; A-side Matrix # AL-35989-1A
          Blue Sky
        - Winx - Left above the clouds (Disc one), 1996; SR-29329; Winx (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29330; SR-29331. Triple album.
          Catalog # XL LP 119; A-side Matrix # XLLP119A MIKE'S-THE EXCHANGE DAMONT
          XL Recordings
        - Winx - Left above the clouds (Disc two), 1996; SR-29330; Winx (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29329; SR-29331. Triple album.
          Catalog # XL LP 119; A-side Matrix # XLLP119C MIKE'S-THE EXCHANGE DAMONT
        - Winx - Left above the clouds (Disc three), 1996; SR-29331; Winx (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29329; SR-29330. Triple album.
          Catalog # XL LP 119; A-side Matrix # XLLP119E MIKE'S-THE EXCHANGE DAMONT
        - W.I.S.E. Guyz - eF yoU eN Kay E, 1989; SR-29333; W.I.S.E. Guyz (Box 79)
          Catalog # 82016-1; A-side Matrix # MASTERDISK TD STA-897427-A 1-1
        - Wiseguys - Casino "Sans Pareil"; A better world, 1997; SR-29334; Wiseguys (Box 79)
          Catalog # WALL T 025; A-side Matrix # SIMON THE EXCHANGE WALL T 025-A1
          Wall of Sound
        - Wiseguys - Mil by mouth, 1995; SR-29335; Wiseguys (Box 79)
          Catalog # WALL T 008; A-side Matrix # 4EVER... WALLT008 A-01-1-1 SIMON- THE EXCHANGE
        - Wish - Touch me (all night long), 1984; SR-29336; Wish; Rae, Fonda (Box 79)
          Catalog # KN 1001; A-side Matrix # KN-1001-12-A
          KN Records
        - Witch Queen - Witch queen, 1979; SR-29337; Witch Queen (Box 79)
          Catalog # BXL1-3312; A-side Matrix # BXL1-3312-A-10